- Maybe I'll do
a cute little button.
- 也许我会做
一个可爱的小按钮。
Or something a bit more manly
perhaps.
或者更有男子气概的东西
也许。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Upturned might be good, too.
朝上也许也不错。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Hi, Squidward.
- 嗨，章鱼哥。
- Great.
The idiot found me.
- 伟大的。
那个白痴发现了我。
- Whatcha doing?
- I'm picking a nose.
- 在做什么？
- 我在抠鼻子。
- Ooh!
I used to pick my nose too,
- 哦！
我也经常挖鼻孔
until I finally
cleared it out.
直到我终于
把它清除了。
- I'm not picking my nose,
SpongeBob.
- 我没有挖鼻孔
海绵宝宝。
I'm on the way to the hospital
for a nose job.
我正在去医院的路上
鼻子整形手术。
Plastic surgery.
整形外科。
I'm finally gonna get
the nose
我终于要得到
鼻子
I should have been born with.
我应该是天生的。
- [gasps] But, Squidward,
you're a beautiful flower.
- [喘气]但是，章鱼哥，
你是一朵美丽的花。
You don't need to change
a--ay--yay--yay--ay--
你不需要改变
啊--哎--耶--耶--哎--
Well, maybe a little work
wouldn't hurt.
好吧，也许需要一点工作
不会受伤。
Hey, you want a ride?
- With you? Absolutely not.
嘿，你想搭车吗？
- 与你？绝对不是。
- Aww, come on, Squidward.
- 哇哦，来吧，章鱼哥。
I can get you there
lickity-split.
我可以带你去那里
舔度分裂。
[siren blaring]
[警笛鸣响]
[both grunting]
[两人都咕哝着]
- You can't dump
your garbage here, sir.
- 你不能倾倒
你的垃圾在这里，先生。
- Oh, that's not garbage.
That's my friend, Squidward.
- 哦，那不是垃圾。
那是我的朋友，章鱼哥。
We're here to check in.
我们是来办理登机手续的。
- Holy nostroly! You must be
here for the nose job.
- 神圣的诺斯特罗利！你一定是
在这里进行鼻子整形手术。
Let's, uh, get your paperwork
filled out.
让我们，呃，拿到你的文件
填写。
- You just relax, sir.
- 你放松点，先生。
The doctor will be ready
for you soon.
医生会准备好
很快就给你了。
- [inhales deeply]
Ah. This is nice.
- [深吸一口气]
啊。这很好。
- Never fear, Squidward.
- 别害怕，章鱼哥。
Soon this dreary old room
will be so full of well-wishing
很快这个沉闷的旧房间
都会充满美好的祝愿
you'll never want to go home.
你永远不想回家。
- Five minutes later.
- 五分钟后。
- [grunting] SpongeBob,
get this garbage out of here.
- [咕哝]海绵宝宝，
把这些垃圾赶出这里。
I can hardly move.
我几乎无法动弹。
- Oh, are you uncomfortable?
Here, let me help.
-哦，你不舒服吗？
在这里，让我帮忙。
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- I love you.
- The bed is fine!
- 我爱你。
- 床很好！
- Fluff your pillow?
- No.
- 弄松你的枕头？
- 不。
- Fluff your IV bag?
- [grunting]
- 弄乱你的静脉输液袋？
- [咕哝]
Enough, you buffoon!
够了，你这个小丑！
- Well, gee, Squidward,
I was just trying to be helpful.
- 嗯，哎呀，章鱼哥，
我只是想帮忙。
- If you want
to help so badly,
- 如果你愿意的话
提供如此严重的帮助，
why don't you just go volunteer
to be a candy striper?
你为什么不去当志愿者呢
成为一名糖果脱衣舞者？
There's plenty of other people
in the hospital
还有很多其他人
在医院
you could torture.
你可以折磨。
- Squidward,
that's a great idea.
- 章鱼哥，
这是个好主意。
I was born to serve.
我生来就是为了服务。
Hello, lady, can I be
a candy striper here at the--
你好，女士，我可以吗
这里有一个糖果条纹工——
- Grab a uniform
out of the closet.
- 穿上制服
从壁橱里出来。
- Ooh, thank you!
Thank you! Whoo!
- 哦，谢谢你！
谢谢你！呼！
Ooh! Candy stripes.
哦！糖果条纹。
[gulps]
Strawberry.
[吞咽]
草莓。
- Ah, Doctor,
Thank goodness you're here.
- 啊，医生，
谢天谢地你还在这里。
- We were just looking
for another physician
- 我们只是在寻找
为另一位医生
to join us on our rounds.
加入我们的巡演。
And what seems to be
the problem today?
以及似乎是什么
今天的问题是什么？
- [coughing]
My throat hurts.
- [咳嗽]
我的喉咙很痛。
- Prescribe him
a numbing throat spray.
- 给他开药
使喉咙麻木的喷雾剂
Let's move on, shall we?
- Wait a second.
我们继续吧，好吗？
- 等一下。
I think
I've seen this before.
我认为
我以前见过这个。
Mm, yeah.
嗯，是的。
Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。
I'll need one medical
sea-chicken.
我需要一名医疗人员
海鸡。
- [squawks]
- [嘎嘎声]
- [giggling, laughing]
- [咯咯笑，大笑]
[coughing]
[咳嗽]
Hey, my keys.
And my throat feels better.
嘿，我的钥匙。
我的喉咙感觉好多了。
- You see, doctors,
catfish are bottom feeders.
- 你看，医生们，
鲶鱼是底层饲养者。
The dirt on his face
led me to believe
他脸上的污垢
让我相信
he had recently eaten something
that irritated his throat.
他最近吃了一些东西
这刺激了他的喉咙。
Happens to my friend Patrick
all the time.
发生在我朋友帕特里克身上
一直。
[grunts]
Mm-hmm.
[咕哝]
嗯嗯。
Try a krabby patty
next time, sir.
尝试蟹肉饼
下次，先生。
They go down smooth, and they
taste better than car keys.
他们进展顺利，而且他们
味道比车钥匙还好。
- Thanks doc.
- No need to thank me, sir.
- 谢谢医生。
- 不用谢我，先生。
I'm here to help.
我是来帮忙的。
- What treatment
might you prescribe
- 什么治疗
你可以开处方吗
for this next patient,
Doctor?
对于下一个病人，
医生？
- So what do you think?
- 那你觉得怎么样？
Will I be able to run
我能跑吗
in the Bikini Bottom marathon
next week?
在比基尼泳裤马拉松中
下周？
- Oh, my, no.
I'm afraid you're--
- 哦，天哪，不。
我担心你是——
- Of course. Friends don't let
friends miss marathons.
- 当然。朋友不让
朋友们怀念马拉松。
We'll have you up
in no time.
我们会扶你起床
很快。
Ah!
啊!
- What are you--
[both grunting]
- 你是什么--
[两人都咕哝着]
- Most unorthodox.
- 最不正统的。
- He's a genius.
- 他是个天才。
- Thanks, doc.
- Ready, set.
- 谢谢，博士。
- 准备好，开始。
[horn blaring]
[喇叭声]
- And what seems to be
your problem today, ma'am?
- 看起来是什么
女士，您今天有什么问题吗？
- Sometimes
I Just don't have it in me
- 有时
我只是没有它在我身上
to puff up
under my own power.
膨胀
在我自己的力量之下。
- Hi, Mrs. Puff.
- No! Not you!
- 嗨，普芙女士。
- 不！不是你！
[whimpering]
What are you doing here?
[呜咽]
你在这里做什么？
- Don't worry, Mrs. Puff.
I'm a doctor...today.
- 别担心，帕芙女士。
我是一名医生……今天。
What is this crazy thing?
这是什么疯狂的事情？
Looks like some sort
of weird submarine.
看起来像是某种
奇怪的潜艇。
- You're kidding,
of course.
- 你在开玩笑吧
当然。
We've placed her in an iron lung
to help puff her back up.
我们把她放进铁肺里
帮助她振作起来。
- Ha-ha! Dive! Dive!
Up periscope!
- 哈哈！潜水！潜水！
潜望镜上来！
Load the torpedoes.
[imitates farting]
装载鱼雷。
[模仿放屁]
[laughing]
[笑]
- Help me.
[screaming]
- 帮我。
[尖叫]
- Hey!
[all screaming]
- 嘿！
[所有人尖叫]
- My legs!
- 我的腿！
- Never fear, Mrs. Puff.
- 别害怕，普夫夫人。
I haven't lost a patient
all day.
我没有失去一个病人
一整天。
Let's get medical.
我们去就医吧
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
- Oh, no.
- 哦，不。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
Oh. Actually, I feel like
my old self again.
哦。其实我觉得
又是我的旧我。
But you still don't get
a driver's license.
但你还是不明白
驾驶执照。
Oh!
哦！
- Wow. I've never seen anyone
work an iron lung like that.
- 哇。我从未见过任何人
像这样工作铁肺。
- So awesome.
- 太棒了。
- We were on our way
to perform a surgery...
- 我们正在路上
进行手术...
- But we would be honored
to watch you perform it.
- 但我们会很荣幸
观看你执行它。
- Me?
Perform a surgery?
- 我？
进行手术吗？
- Oh, yeah,
this is the life.
- 哦，是的，
这就是生活。
And best of all, there's no
SpongeBob here to ruin it.
最重要的是，没有
海绵宝宝来毁掉它。
- Oh, boy, surgery.
And on my first day too.
- 哦，孩子，手术。
我的第一天也是如此。
- SpongeBob? No!
What are you doing here?
- 海绵宝宝？不！
你在这里做什么？
- Nighty night,
Mr. Tentacles.
- 晚安的夜晚，
触手先生。
- Wait, wait, no, no, no, no!
- 等等，等等，不，不，不，不！
[snoring]
[打鼾]
- Oh, hi, everybody.
all: Hi, SpongeBob.
- 噢，大家好。
全体：嗨，海绵宝宝。
- Doctor,
the patient's over here,
- 医生，
病人在这里
and he's ready for you
to begin.
他已经为你准备好了
开始。
- Oh, we're most eager to see
which tool you select first.
- 哦，我们最渴望看到
您首先选择哪个工具。
- Hmm, mm--mm-mm--mm.
Let me see.
- 嗯，毫米--毫米-毫米--毫米。
让我看看。
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Phew.
哇哇哇！
唷。
Here we go.
开始了。
[triumphant music]
[胜利的音乐]
[yawning]
[打哈欠]
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
all: Ooh!
Ah!
全体：噢！
啊!
- Okay, SpongeBob,
this can't be too hard.
- 好吧，海绵宝宝，
这不会太难。
Just make an incision here,
and--no!
在这里切个切口就可以了
还有——不！
Shoot!
Son of a gun!
射击！
枪之子！
Ah, my bad.
啊，我的错。
- I'll take that.
- 我会接受的。
- Ah-ha! Mmm, sushi.
- 啊哈！嗯，寿司。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Eeh.
呃。
He's uh, really going to pieces
over this nose job.
他呃，真的要崩溃了
关于这个鼻子整形手术。
[laughter]
[笑声]
Oh. [chuckles]
Thank you.
哦。 [笑声]
谢谢你。
Let's try again, shall we?
我们再试一次，好吗？
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
Order up!
赶快下单吧！
[laughter and applause]
[笑声和掌声]
Yow!
That shouldn't be in there.
哟！
那不应该在那里。
Ooh!
哦！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
What?
什么？
Oh.
哦。
- Ta-da!
- 哒哒！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
Nurse, sponge.
护士，海绵。
- [giggling]
- [咯咯笑]
- Thank you, nurse.
- 谢谢你，护士。
- I can't see!
I can't see!
- 我看不到！
我看不见！
I want to see!
[grunting]
我想看看！
[咕噜声]
I still can't see.
我还是看不清。
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[organ music]
[管风琴音乐]
- Ta da!
- 哒哒！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
[humming]
[嗡嗡声]
There we go.
我们开始吧。
You can wake him up now,
nurse.
你现在可以叫醒他了
护士。
- [groaning]
What--what happened?
- [呻吟]
发生了什么事？
- I finished your nose job,
you silly goose.
- 我完成了你的鼻子整形手术
你这个傻鹅。
Take a look.
看看吧。
- SpongeBob, you idiot.
- 海绵宝宝，你这个白痴。
This isn't even close
to what I wanted.
这还差得很远
到我想要的。
- Well, why didn't you say so?
Oh, nurse!
- 那么，你为什么不这么说呢？
哦，护士！
- Wait, no, no, no!
I want a different doctor. I--
- 等等，不，不，不！
我想要一个不同的医生。我 -
No.
不。
No!
No.
不！
不。
No.
No--o--o--o--o!
不。
不——哦——哦——哦——哦！
Stop! I don't want to change
my nose anymore.
停止！我不想改变
我的鼻子了。
SpongeBob, I'll do anything.
Anything at--
海绵宝宝，我愿意做任何事。
任何事情都在——
- How's about
the Squidward Classic?
- 怎么样
章鱼哥经典？
- Hey, not bad.
- 嘿，还不错。
This looks even better
than my old nose.
这看起来更好
比我的老鼻子
- Well, I did have to use
a few of your other body parts
- 好吧，我确实必须使用
你身体的一些其他部位
to re-sculpt it.
重新雕刻它。
D'oh! Look at the time.
I have to go to work.
噢！看看时间。
我得去上班了。
- But you're a doctor.
You're at work.
- 但你是一名医生。
你正在工作。
- No, I'm just a fry cook.
- 不，我只是个炒菜的厨师。
But it was fun
playing with you guys. Bye!
但这很有趣
和你们一起玩。再见！
- Fry cook?
Ooh.
- 炒菜做饭？
哦。
- Don't be afraid, ladies.
- 别害怕，女士们。
This sinus Adonis
is on the market.
这窦阿多尼斯
已上市。
[both gasping]
[两人都喘气]